Ruzhytskyi Dmytro Full stack developer Edinburgh, UK +447831417609

dmitruz970@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dmytro-ruzhytskyi/

Telegram: Dmytro Ruzhytskyi (0970296162)

https://github.com/dmitruz

### **Summary**

Motivated and development oriented person with experience in Frontend and Backend development. I am keen on writing clean and mutable code for building my applications. My experience ranges from pure HTML, CSS, JavaScript development to React framework and basic Node.js development.

I get on well with people at all levels, can easily make good working relationships.

#### **Technical Skills:**

Frontend languages: CSS3, HTML5, JS, XML, BEM, SASS. Frameworks: React, Bootstrap, Redux, Material UI.

Backend languages: Node.js, Express.js.

Databases: SQL database.

Task and Project Management: Git.

Tools: Photoshop, NPM, Webpack, Eslint, Gulp, Figma, VSCode, JMeter, Trello.

#### **Portfolio**

Web Studio [HTML, CSS, SASS, BEM] Mobile-first adaptive landing page to introduce web studio with order form. <a href="https://github.com/dmitruz/goit-markup-hw-08">https://github.com/dmitruz/goit-markup-hw-08</a> <a href="https://dmitruz.github.io/goit-markup-hw-08">https://dmitruz.github.io/goit-markup-hw-08</a>/

Mobile-first adaptive web site, searching movies. (Team project) [HTML, SASS, JS, Node.js, API, REST, Parsel]

 $\underline{\text{https://github.com/dmitruz/filmoteka-team-project}} \ \underline{\text{https://dmitruz.github.io/filmoteka-team-project/}} \\ \underline{\text{project/}}$ 

Weather forecast application [HTML, CSS, JS, API, Parsel]

https://github.com/dmitruz/Weather forecast/

## **Experience**

Position: Freelance Frontend developer. 02.2022 – present.

Company: UpWork

Duties: Created web pages, applications, landing pages, updated content.

Position: Engineer 06.2010 – 12.2018. Company: Dunaivtsi State Forest Land

Duties: Organized preparation of land for planting siblings and seeds. Led deforestation on the site. Calculated average height and value of trees and timber. Processed data and sent to database. Worked with Gis.

# **Education**

National University of Life and Environmental Science in Ukraine. Kyiv, Ukraine (2004 2010) Master of Science

IT school Golt. Kyiv, Ukraine (05.2021 – 07.2022) Full stack developer.

Languages: English: Excellent.

Ukrainian: Native.